Guide to the New-York Historical Society Postcard Collection [graphic] circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950) PR 54
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Geographic Locations | United States (except New York), circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950); 21.39 Linear feet (in 39.5 boxes)
  - Pennsylvania (continued) (Box 76)
    Washington
    Wilkes-Barre
    Williamsport
    X-Z
    Pennsylvania Highways
  - Pennsylvania | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-A)
    American Swedish Historical Museum, Philadelphia (2)
    Anthracite Coal Mines
    Friendship Hill (home of Albert Gallatin)
    Hershey
    Philadelphia (2)
    Sesqui-Centennial and Philadelphia
  - Pennsylvania | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 1))
  - Pennsylvania | Miniature (Box 98)
  - Rhode Island (Box 77)
    Block Island
    C-G
    H-N
    Narragansett Pier
    Hurricane, 1938
    Old Stone Mill
    Providence
    Athenaeum
    Brown University
    Q-T
    Watch Hill
    Westerly
  - Rhode Island | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
    Newport (3; one showing extent of damage from 1938 New England Hurricane)
  - Rhode Island | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 1))
  - South Carolina (Box 77)
    Charleston
    Battery
    Gardens
    Powder Magazine
    Columbia
  - South Carolina | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
    Magnolia Gardens
  - South Dakota (Box 78)
  - Tennessee (Box 78)
    Chattanooga
    Memphis
    Nashville
  - Tennessee | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
    Morris Dam and Tennessee Valley
  - Texas (Box 78-79)
    Dallas
    E-F
    Fort Worth
    G-H
    Houston
    I-M
    San Antonio
  - Texas | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
    Corpus Christi
  - Utah (Box 79)
    Bryce Canyon
    Cedar Breaks
    Salt Lake City
    Mormon Temple and Tabernacle
    State Capitol
    Zion National Park
  - Utah | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 1))
  - Vermont (Box 80-81)
    Bellows Falls
    Bennington
    Brattleboro
    Burlington
    C-L
    Lake Bomoseen
    Manchester
    Windsor
    Woodstock
  - Vermont | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 1))
  - Virginia (Box 81)
    Alexandria
    Arlington
    Ash Lawn
    Charlottesville
  - Virginia (continued) (Box 82)
    D-F
    Fredericksburg
    Fort Monroe
    G-K
    Hampton
    Hot Springs
    Jamestown
    Luray
    Monticello
  - Virginia (continued) (Box 83)
    Mount Vernon
    Natural Bridge
    Newport News
    Norfolk
    Richmond
    Monuments and Memorials
  - Virginia (continued) (Box 84)
    Williamsburg
    Winchester
    Yorktown
  - Virginia | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
    Arlington (3)
    Historic Virginia Churches (3)
    Kenmore, Fredericksburg
    Mariner's Museum, Newport News
    Mount Vernon (5)
    Shenandoah National Park and Skyline Drive
    Williamsburg (3)
  - Washington (Box 84)
    Lake Washington
    Mount Washington
    Ranier National Park
    Seattle
    Spokane
    Tacoma
  - Washington | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
  - Washington | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 1))
  - West Virginia (Box 84)
    Harper's Ferry
  - Wisconsin (Box 85)
    H-M
    Lake Superior
    Milwaukee
    Wisconsin River
  - Wyoming (Box 85)
    Yellowstone National Park
  - Wyoming | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
    Overland Route
    Wild Animals of Yellowstone Park
  - United States, general | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
    Images of the Civil War
    U.S. Military
  - United States | Unidentified locations (Box 85)
- Series II. Geographic Locations | New York, circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950); 27.89 Linear feet (in 51.5 boxes)
  - Subseries II.A. New York State, circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950); 14.89 Linear feet (in 27.5 boxes)
    - New York State (Box 25-26)
      Adirondack Mountains
      Ausable Chasm
      John Brown's Homestead and Grave
      Tupper Lake
    - New York State (continued) (Box 26-27)
      Albany
      Historic
      Hotels and Restaurants
      Schuyler Mansion
      State Capitol Exterior
      State Capitol Interior
      State Education Building
    - New York State (continued) (Box 27)
      Am-At
      Au-Az
      Auburn
      B-Be
      Babylon
      Ballston Spa
      Bath
      Bay Shore
      Beacon
      Bear Mountain
    - New York State (continued) (Box 28)
      Bi-Bu
      Binghamton
      Club Buildings
      Court House and Square
      Hospitals and Homes
      Office Buildings
      Parks and Rivers
      Public Buildings
      Streets
      Bloominburg
      Bo-Bz
      Buffalo
      Albright Art Gallery
      Squares
    - New York State (continued) (Box 29)
      C-Cal
      Cam-Car
      Campville
      Canajoharie
      Canandaigua
      Cas-Caz
      Catskill
      Catskills & Catskill Mountains
      Ashokan Reservoir
      Kaaterskill (Falls, Lake, etc.)
      Rip Van Winkle House, etc.
      Catskill Mountains General
    - New York State (continued) (Box 30)
      Ce-Cl
      Chappaqua
      Chautauqua
      Cherry Valley
      Clifton Springs
      Sanitarium
      Clinton
      Co
      Cooperstown
      Baseball Museum
      Bodies of Water
      Cooper, James F.: grave, monument, statue, etc.
      Cooper Park
      Farmers' Museum
      Hotels and O-te-sa-ga (Knox School)
      New York State Historical Association
    - New York State (continued) (Box 31)
      Corning
      Cornwall
      Cr-Cz
      Cragsmoor
      Crown Point
      Da-De
      Dansville
      Deposit
      Di-Do
      Dr-Du
      E-Ed
      East Hampton
      El-Es
    - New York State (continued) (Box 32)
      Ellenville
      Elmira
      Essex
      Et-Ez
      F-Fi
      Finger Lakes
      Fire Island
      Light House
      Ocean Beach
      Point O'Woods
      Saltaire
      Fishers Island
      Fishkill
      Fl-Fo
      Florida
    - New York State (continued) (Box 33)
      Fort Ticonderoga
      Fr-Fz
      Fulton
      Ga-Ge
      Geneva
      Gi-Gl
      Glens Falls
    - New York State (continued) (Box 34)
      Go-Gr
      Goshen
      Greenport
      Greenwood Lake
      Ha
      Haines Falls
      Hamilton
      He
      Hi
      Ho
      Homer
      Hu
      Hudson
    - New York State (continued) (Box 35)
      Hudson River
      Anthony's Nose
      Breakneck Mountain
      Crow's Nest Mountain
      Highlands
      Indian Point
      Islands
      Stony Points
      Storm King Highway
      Storm King Mountain
      Sugar Loaf Mountain
      Huntington
      Hurley
      Hyde Park
      I
      Ithaca
      Cornell University
    - New York State (continued) (Box 36)
      J
      Johnstown
      Ka-Ke
      Ki-Kz
      Kinderhook
      Kingston
      Kingston Point
      Restaurants and Taverns
      Senate House
      L-Lak
      Lake _____
      Lake Champlain
    - New York State (continued) (Box 36-37)
      Lake George
      Bays
      Forts
      Glenburnie
      Glen Eyrie
      Lake George Village
      Lake Minnewaska
      Lake Placid
      Lake Ronkonkoma
      Lal-Laz
      Le-Li
      Liberty
    - New York State (continued) (Box 38)
      Lo
      Lockport
      Locust Valley
      Lowville
      Lu-Ly
      Mc
      Ma
      Mahopac
      Malden
      Matteawan
      Me
    - New York State (continued) (Box 39)
      Mi
      Middleburg(h)
      Middletown
      Mo
      Mohegan
      Mohonk Lake
      Montauk
      Mount Kisco
      Mount Lebanon
      Mount McGregor
      Mu
      Na-Ne
    - New York State (continued) (Box 39-40)
      Newburgh
    - New York State (continued) (Box 61-62)
      New Paltz
      New Rochelle
      Ni
      Niagara Falls
    - New York State (continued) (Box 62)
      No-Nz
      Northport
      Nyack
      Oa-Og
      Oh-On
      Olean
      Oneonta
      Op-Oq
      Or-Os
      Oscawana
    - New York State (continued) (Box 63)
      Ossining
      Oswego
      Ot-Oz
      Otsego Lake
      Owego
      Oyster Bay
      Pa
      Palmyra
      Patchogue
      Paul Smiths
      Pawling
      Pe-Ph
      Peekskill
      Penn Yan
      Pi-Pl
      Plattsburg
      Pleasantville
    - New York State (continued) (Box 64)
      Po
      Port Chester
      Port Jefferson
      Port Jervis
      Port Washington
      Poughkeepsie
      Vassar College
      Pr-Pu
      Q
      Ra-Re
      Red Hook
      Rensselaer
      Rh-Ri
      Rhinebeck
      Richfield Springs
      Riverhead
    - New York State (continued) (Box 65)
      Ro-Rz
      Rochester
      Genesee River and Erie Canal
      Rome
      Roscoe
      Rosendale
      Roxbury
      Churches and Schools
      Historical Pageant
      Rye
      Sa
      Sag Harbor
      Saint James
      Saint Johnsville
      Sampson
    - New York State (continued) (Box 66)
      Saranac Lake
      Hospitals and Sanitaria
      Winter Sports and Carnivals
      Saratoga Springs
      Race Track
      Saratoga Lake
      Spas
    - New York State (continued) (Box 67)
      Saugerties
      Sc
      Schenectady
      Union College
      Schoharie
      Schuylerville
      Se-Sh
      Sea Cliff
      Setauket
      Sharon Springs
      Shawangunk & Shawangunk Mountains
      Shelter Island
      Skaneateles
      Si-Sn
    - New York State (continued) (Box 68-69)
      So
      Sp
      Spring Valley
      Stony Brook
      Stony Point
      St
      Su-Sz
      Syracuse
      Canals and Railroads
      Clinton Square
      Parks and Monuments
      Salt Works
      State Fair
      Syracuse University
    - New York State (continued) (Box 69)
      Ta
      Tappan
      Andre "76" House and Monument
      Washington House
      Tarrytown
      Andre Monument
      Philipse Castle
      Sunnyside
      Te-To
      Thousand Islands
      Alexandria Bay
      Heart Island
      Ticonderoga
      Tr-Tz
      Troy
    - New York State (continued) (Box 70)
      U
      Utica
      Streets and Views
      Waterways
      V
      Valhalla
      Wa
      Wappingers Falls
      Warwick
      Watertown
      Watkins Glen
    - New York State (continued) (Box 71)
      We
      West Hebron
      West Point Military Academy
      Cadets
      Westport
      Wh-Wi
      White Lake
      White Plains
      Wo-Wu
      Wurtsboro
      Y
      Yonkers
      Youngsville
      Yulan
      New York State General
    - New York State | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-B)
      Adirondack Mountains (6)
      Albany (14)
      Ashokan-Gilboa Reservoirs (1)
      Auburn (1)
      Auriesville / National Shrine, North American Martyrs (4)
      Ausable Chasm (8)
      Bear Mountain (7)
      Binghamton (2)
      Buffalo (3)
      Catskill Mountains (2)
      Chatauqua (2)
      Chenango Trail (1)
      Cherry Valley (1)
      Clifton Springs (1)
      Elmira (1)
      Finger Lakes (3)
      Fire Island (1)
      Fort Ticonderoga (10)
      Fultonville (1)
      Geneva (1)
      Glen Cove (1)
    - New York State | Souvenir Folders & Sets (continued) (Box 96-C)
      Hudson River (10)
      Huntington (1)
      Ithaca and Cornell University (2)
      Lake George (6)
      Lake Placid (3)
      Lily Dale (1)
      Lockport (1)
      Long Beach (1)
      Long Lake (3)
      Montauk (3)
      Newburgh (1)
      Niagara Falls (15)
      Rochester (2)
      Rye Playland (1)
      Saranac Lake (1)
      Saratoga Springs and Battlefield (3)
      Schenectady (3)
      Schroon Lake (1)
      Skaneateles (1)
      Storm King Highway (6)
      Syracuse (4)
      Thousand Islands (1)
      Troy (1)
      Utica (2)
      Watkins Glen (3)
      West Point (10)
      White Plains (1)
      Yonkers (1)
    - New York State | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 2))
    - New York State | Miniature (Box 98)
      Adirondack Mountains (2)
      Albany (2)
      Ashokan Reservoir (1)
      Ausable Chasm (1)
      Buffalo (1)
      Catskill Mountains (1)
      Hudson River (2)
      Ithaca (1)
      Kingston (1)
      Niagara Falls (2)
      Seneca Falls (1)
      Tupper Lake (2)
      Watkins Glen (2)
  - Subseries II.B. New York City, circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950); 13 Linear feet (in 24 boxes)
    - New York City | Greetings from... (Box 40)
    - New York City | Bridges (Box 40-41)
      A-Z
      Brooklyn Bridge
      George Washington Bridge
      Goethals Bridge
      Hell Gate Bridge
      High Bridge
      Manhattan Bridge
      Queensboro Bridge
      Triboro Bridge
      Verrazano-Narrows Bridge
      Washington Bridge
      Williamsburg Bridge
      Viaducts
    - New York City | Celebrations (Box 41)
      Parades, A-Z
      Bicentennial
      Hudson-Fulton Celebration
      Churchman Series
      Redfield Series
      World's Fair, 1939
      Art
      Commercial
      Foreign
      States
      Trylon & Perisphere
      World's Fair, 1964–65
    - New York City | Celebrations | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-D)
      World's Fair, 1964-65
    - New York City | Future (Box 42)
    - New York City | History (Box 42)
      1492-1663
      1664-1799
      1800-present
    - New York City | Humor (Box 42)
    - New York City | Islands (Box 42)
      Ellis Island
      Governor's Island
      Liberty Island (and Statue of Liberty)
      Randall's Island
      Roosevelt Island (formerly Blackwell's and Welfare Island)
    - New York City | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-D)
      Includes "Souvenir Folder of New York, The City of Wonders" (Manhattan Card Publishing Co.), the gift of Analee Wulfkuhle (accession no. PPAC.2018.024). Ms. Wulfkuhle's mother, Ella Jean Skidmore, traveled to New York City with her Topeka (Kansas) High School classmates in 1936, and marked with a check in the souvenir folder each sight she saw. Inserted in the folder is a postcard of the George Washington Bridge, postmarked 1933, and sent by Ella Jean to a Skidmore relative in Carbondale, Kansas.
    - New York City | Miniature (Box 98)
      General (13)
      World's Fair, 1939 (1)
      World's Fair, 1964-65 (1)
    - Manhattan | Apartment Houses (Box 42)
    - Manhattan | Armories (Box 42)
    - Manhattan | Banks (Box 42)
    - Manhattan | Building construction (Box 42)
    - Manhattan | Buildings (two or more) (Box 42)
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (A) (Box 43)
      Adams Express Building
      American Radiator Building
      American Surety Building
      American Tract Society Building
      Astor Trust Building
      Aquarium
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (B) (Box 43)
      Bank of Manhattan Building
      Bankers Trust Building
      Barclay Vesey Building
      Bible House
      Broadway-Chambers Building
      Bowling Green Building
      Bush Terminal Sales Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (C) (Box 43)
      Canadian Pacific Building
      Cartier's Building
      Chanin Building
      Chase Manhattan Plaza
      Cities Service Building
      City Bank Farmers Trust Building
      Coliseum
      Commercial Cable Building
      Consolidated Gas Company Building
      Cunard Building
      multiple cards
      Chamber of Commerce
      Chrysler Building
      City Investing Building
      Civic Center
      Clearing House
      Custom House
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (D) (Box 43)
      Daily News Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (E) (Box 43)
      Equitable Building
      Equitable Life Assurance Society
      Equitable Trust Company Building
      Esso Building
      Emigrant Building & Barge Office
      Empire Building
      Empire State Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (F) (Box 44)
      Federal Reserve
      Fifth Avenue Building
      Fisk Tire Building
      500 Fifth Avenue Building
      42nd Street and Lexington Avenue Tower
      Fred L. French Building
      Flatiron (Fuller) Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (G) (Box 44)
      General Electric Building
      General Motors Building
      Grand Central Palace
      Graybar Building
      Gillender Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (H) (Box 44)
      Hayden Planetarium
      Heckscher Building
      Herald Building
      Hall of Records (Surrogate's Court)
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (I) (Box 44)
      International House
      Irving Trust Company Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (L) (Box 44)
      Lever House
      Liberty Tower
      Liggett's Building
      Lincoln Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (M) (Box 44)
      Maiden Lane Building
      Masonic Building (Sixth Avenue & 23rd Street)
      Mecca Temple
      Metropolitan Building
      J. Pierpont Morgan Building
      Municipal Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (N) (Box 44)
      New York Central Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (P) (Box 44)
      Pan Am Building
      Paramount Building
      Park Lexington Building
      Pershing Square Building
      Postal Telegraph and Home Life Building
      Presbyterian Building (156 Fifth Avenue)
      Park Row Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (R) (Box 44)
      Rockefeller Center
      (Radio City Music Hall under Manhattan | Theaters & Entertainment Venues, box 55-C)
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (S) (Box 45)
      Schermerhorn Row (South Street Seaport)
      Sinclair Oil Building
      Sixty Wall Tower
      Sixty-three Wall Street Building
      Smith, Gray & Co.
      Staats Zeitung
      St. Paul Building
      Singer Building
      Standard Oil Building
      Sub-Treasury Building (Federal Hall)
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (T) (Box 45)
      Tammany Hall
      Transportation Building
      29 Broadway
      Telephone Building(s)
      Times Building
      Tribune Building
      Trinity Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (U) (Box 45)
      U.S. Express Building
      United Nations
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named (W) (Box 45)
      One Wall Street Building
      Washington Building
      Washington Life Building
      West Street Building (Little Woolworth Building)
      World Building
      World Government House
      World Tower Building
      World Trade Center
      Whitehall Building
      Woolworth Building
    - Manhattan | Buildings, named | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-D)
      Metropolitan Opera House
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (A) (Box 46)
      All Angels' (Episcopal, 428 West End Avenue) [interior]
      Annunciation (Greek Orthodox, 310 West 54th) [interior]
      Ascension (Episcopal, Fifth Avenue & West 10th) [exterior & interior]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (B) (Box 46)
      Brick Presbyterian (412 Fifth Avenue) [old & new]
      Broadway Tabernacle (Broadway United Church of Christ, 1750 Broadway) [exterior & interior]
      Broadway Temple United Church of Christ (4111 Broadway) [skyscraper church]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (C) (Box 46)
      Calvary Baptist (123 West 57th)
      Calvary Methodist Episcopal (now Salem United Methodist, 211 West 129th)
      Camp Memorial Church (141 Chrystie Street)
      Cenacle of St. Regis (628 West 140th) [exterior & interior]
      Central Baptist (220 West 42nd)
      Corpus Christi (Roman Catholic, 533 West 121st) [exterior & interior]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (E) (Box 46)
      Emanuel Baptist (47 Suffolk)
      Epiphany (Episcopal, 257 Lexington Avenue) [interior]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (F) (Box 46)
      Fifteenth Street Meeting House (Quaker, 15 Rutherford Place)
      Fifth Avenue Presbyterian (7 West 55th) [exterior & interior]
      First Church of Christ, Scientist (1 West 96th)
      First German Reformed (later First Alliance Church, 351 East 68th)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (G) (Box 46)
      German Evangelical Reformed [or Christ Lutheran?] (69-71 Avenue B @ East 5th)
      Grace Church (Episcopal, 800 Broadway) [exterior & interior]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (H) (Box 46)
      Heavenly Rest (Episcopal, 551 Fifth Avenue)
      Holy Communion (Episcopal, 47 West 20th) [interior]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (I) (Box 46)
      Incarnation (Episcopal, 209 Madison Avenue) [exterior & interior]
      Intercession, Chapel [now Church] of the (Episcopal, 3801 Broadway)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (J) (Box 46)
      John Street Church (Methodist, 44 John Street) [exterior & interior & first building]
      Judson Memorial Church (American Baptist, 55 Washington Square South)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (L) (Box 46)
      "Little Church Around the Corner" (see Transfiguration)
      "Little Church of Everybody" (replica of an Italian church constructed by Domenico Zazzera in his home at 837 Second Avenue)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (M) (Box 46)
      Madison Avenue Methodist Episcopal (655 Madison Avenue)
      Madison Avenue Presbyterian (921 Madison Avenue)
      Madison Square Presbyterian ("Dr. Parkhurst's Church, 7 Madison Avenue)
      Marble Collegiate (Dutch Reformed, 1 West 29th @ Fifth Avenue)
      Metropolitan Temple (Methodist Episcopal, Middle Collegiate (Dutch Reformed, 1731 structure, Nassau Street)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (N) (Box 46)
      New Thought Church (New Aeolian Hall, 32 West 43rd)
      North Presbyterian Church (155th Street between Broadway& Amsterdam)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (O) (Box 46)
      Our Lady of Esperanza (Roman Catholic, 624 West 156th)
      Our Lady of Pompeii (Roman Catholic, 214 Bleecker Street)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (P) (Box 46)
      Perry Street Methodist (132 Perry Street)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (R) (Box 46)
      Riverside Church (American Baptist / United Church of Christ, 490 Riverside Drive) [exterior & interior]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (S) (Box 46)
      Sacred Heart, Convent of the (Roman Catholic, 1 East 91st) [exterior & interior]
      St. Agnes Chapel (Episcopal, 190 West 92nd) [exterior & interior]
      St. Agnes Church (Roman Catholic, 141 East 43rd)
      St. Bartholomew's (Episcopal, 325 Park Avenue)
      St. Charles Borromeo (Roman Catholic, 211 West 141st)
      St.-Esprit, Eglise Francaise du (109 East 60th)
      St. Francis Xavier (Roman Catholic, 30 West 16th)
      St. George (Episcopal, 209 East 16th) [exterior & organ]
      St. Ignatius of Antioch (Episcopal, 56 West 40th) [interior]
      St. James (Episcopal, 865 Madison Avenue) [interior]
      St. Jean Baptiste (Roman Catholic, 184 East 76th) [interior]
      St. John the Evangelist (Episcopal, 220 West 11th)
      St. Luke in the Fields (Episcopal, 487 Hudson Street)
      St. Luke's Lutheran (233 West 42nd)
      St. Mark's Lutheran (now Community Synagogue, 325 East 6th)
      St. Martin's Episcopal (230 Malcolm X Boulevard)
      St. Mary the Virgin (Episcopal, 139 West 46th) [interior]
      St. Nicholas, Collegiate (Dutch Reformed, 600 Fifth Avenue)
      St. Paul the Apostle (Roman Catholic, 10 Columbus Avenue)
      St. Peter's (Episcopal, 344 West 20th)
      St. Peter's (Lutheran, 631 Lexington Avenue)
      St. Peter's (Roman Catholic, 22 Barclay Street) [interior]
      S | multiple cards
      St. John the Divine (Episcopal, 1047 Amsterdam Avenue) [exterior & interior]
      St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery (Episcopal, 131 East 10th Street) [exterior & Stuyvesant window]
      St. Patrick's Cathedral (Roman Catholic, 625 Fifth Avenue) [exterior & interior]
      St. Paul's Chapel (Episcopal, 209 Broadway) [exterior & interior]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (S) (continued) (Box 47)
      St. Thomas (Episcopal, 1 West 53rd) [old & new buildings; exterior & interior]
      Billy Sunday's Tabernacle (Broadway & 168th Street; a portrait of Sunday is filed in box 91)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (T) (Box 47)
      Transfiguration / "Little Church Around the Corner" (Episcopal, 1 East 29th)
      Trinity Church (Episcopal, Broadway at Wall Street) [old & new; exterior & interior]
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues (U) (Box 47)
      Union Reformed Church (Dutch Reformed), 325 Sixth Avenue
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues | Multi-church views (Box 47)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues | Synagogues (Box 47)